kendrascott.com 2019-07-13

# Privacy Policy Disclosure Agreement | Kendra Scott

## _Kendra Scott, LLC_

Last Revision: June 1, 2019

## Introduction

Kendra Scott, LLC and its respective parent companies and/or subsidiaries as applicable (collectively “Kendra Scott”) values its customers and respects their privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information that we collect from and about you when you visit our website, [www.kendrascott.com](http://www.kendrascott.com/) or when you visit one of our retail locations, as well as how we may use, share, and disclose that information. Your use of the website or your purchase from one of our retail locations signifies your assent to this Privacy Policy. For residents from the European Economic Area, Kendra Scott is the data controller responsible for your personal data. 

## Quick Guide to Contents

  * 1\. Information We Collect
  * 2\. Information Use
  * 3\. Information Disclosure
  * 4\. Service Providers
  * 5\. Our Commitment to Data Security
  * 6\. Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy
  * 7\. European Residents
  * 8\. How to Contact Us
  * 9\. Revisions to This Policy

## Information We Collect

### Information You Provide

Kendra Scott collects information from you when you choose to provide it to us, such as when you make a purchase, create an account, sign up for our email list, provide a product review or rating, or otherwise contact us. As described in more detail below, the information we collect may include your name, billing and shipping address(es), email address, payment card information, phone number, birthdate, account user name and password, and product rating or review. If you refuse to provide any requested information (whether or not required), you may not be able to take full advantage of any in-store services, the website or its features.

  * _Make a Purchase_ : Through the website at any of our retail locations, you will be able to purchase Kendra Scott products. We may ask for your name, billing and shipping address(es), telephone number, email address, and payment card information in order to process and confirm your order and ship your item(s) to you. 
  * _Create an Account_[1]: Through the website, you may create a personal shipping account with Kendra Scott, which can make the shipping process faster and easier. Kendra Scott will store the following information in your account, should you choose to provide it to us: your name, billing and shipping address(es), email address, phone number, and birthdate. Kendra Scott may also store your credit card information should you chose to enable this feature. To establish an account, you will need to create a user name and a password that will allow access to the account, where you can add, delete, or change the information you have provided. If you elect to use a public computer to access your account, please remember to log out at the conclusion of your session. 
  * _Email List_ : Through the website or at any retail location, you may add your email address to the Kendra Scott email list. Kendra Scott will never share your email address with, or sell your email address to, a third party that is not a Service Provider (as defined below) or that is otherwise directly or indirectly affiliated with Kendra Scott. You may opt out of receiving marketing emails from Kendra Scott at any time by selecting the “unsubscribe” option within the email or contacting us at [service@kendrascott.com.](mailto:service@kendrascott.com)
  * _Ratings and Reviews_ : Through the website, you may provide a public rating or review of a product you purchased. You are required to provide your email address when you provide a public rating or review. We will not publish your email address, but please remember that any information you may disclose in these public areas of the website becomes public information. As a result, please exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these public areas. 
  * _Customer Service_ : If you engage with our Customer Service center by phone at 1-866-677-7023 or by email, you may be asked for information such as your name, email address, billing and shipping address(es), telephone number, and order number (if you have made a purchase). We use this information to assist you and address your needs.

### Information Automatically or Passively Collected

We may use cookies, pixel tags, or other technologies to automatically or passively collect certain information when you use this website or interact with our emails and online advertisements.

  * _Cookies_ : Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive and used to collect information about your activities on the website. These cookies provide statistical data that helps us to improve our website and deliver better and more customized services. 
  * _Pixel Tags_ : Pixel tags are tiny graphic images on that help us analyze customer online behavior and measure the effectiveness of our website and advertising.

For example, we may automatically collect statistical information such as your IP address, operating system, browser type, and other technical information about your computer or device. We also may collect information about your use of the website, including the identity of the website that referred you to our website; the pages you view; the features you use; the links you click; the date and time you access the website; whether you receive, open, forward, or click-through emails and advertisements; and other usage data.

We also work with third-party business partners (“Service Providers”) that use tracking technologies to deliver advertisements on our behalf across the Internet. These companies may collect information about your visits to our website and your interaction with our advertising and other communications.

_Tracking Options and California Do Not Track Disclosures._

You have the ability to set your browser to limit the tracking described above, or to refuse cookies, as well as to remove cookies from your hard drive, but by doing so, you may not be able to take full advantage of all of our offerings. Check the “Help” menu of your browser or operating system to learn how to change your tracking settings or cookie preferences. To learn more about the use of cookies or other technologies to deliver more relevant advertising and your choices about not having this information used by certain Service Providers, please click here. On your mobile device, you can adjust your privacy and advertising settings to limit your tracking for advertising or control whether you receive more relevant advertising. Note that our systems may not recognize Do Not Track headers or requests from some or all browsers.

### Combination of Information

We may combine the information we receive from and about you, including information you provide to us online or at one of our retail locations and information we automatically or passively collect, to improve our website, to personalize your online experience, to help us deliver information to you, to determine the effectiveness of our advertising, and for other internal business purposes.

## Information Use

We may use the information we collect from and about you for various purposes, such as to provide services, process transactions, improve customer experience and engagement, and develop the website. We will have a lawful basis for processing your information if:

  * We need to process your information to provide you with products or service you have requested or to enter into a contract;
  * You have consented to such processing;
  * We have a legitimate interest for processing your data, like analytics, fraud prevention, improving the website and our business, and direct marketing; and/or we are legally required to process it.

We may use the information we collect from and about you for purposes including but not limited to the following:

  * Provide services and communicate with website visitors;
  * Process transactions;
  * Improve our website and your customer shopping experience;
  * Send communications about our products, services, and promotions;
  * Respond to your inquiries;
  * Contact you when necessary;
  * Prevent and detect fraud and abuse; and/or as described to you at the point of collection.

We may store this information for as long as is reasonably necessary to accomplish these tasks, unless the law permits or requires a longer period. For example, if you create an account, we may store any information associated with your account even after cancellation of your account. If you make a purchase, we will store any personal information associated with that purchase for as long as necessary to fulfill the order and process any returns.

## Information Disclosure

We may disclose the information we collect from and about you (1) to our Service Providers, if the disclosure will enable them to perform a business, professional, or technical support function for us; (2) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of our rights or the rights of any third party; (3) to respond to judicial process or provide information to law enforcement or regulatory agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; and (4) as described to you at the point of collection. We do not sell the information we collect to any non-affiliated third parties.

Kendra Scott may sell or purchase assets during the normal course of our business. If another entity acquires us or any of our assets, information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity. In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use the information provided through the website in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

## Service Providers

We may contract with Service Providers to perform functions related to the website. Such Service Providers will have access to the information collected as necessary to perform their business functions for Kendra Scott, some of which are described in this Policy, but may not use or share that information for purposes outside the scope of those business functions.

## Our Commitment to Data Security

Kendra Scott goes to great lengths to keep financial information private and safe, and we take certain physical, electronic, and administrative steps to maintain the security and accuracy of all the information we collect from and about website visitors and users.

While we will use every reasonable means to help ensure the security and integrity of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee our security measures.

## Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

Protecting children’s privacy is important to us. We do not direct the website to, nor do we knowingly, collect any information from children under the age of thirteen (13).

## European Residents

Residents of the European Economic Area have the following rights with respect to the personal information collected from and about you on the website:

  * The right to request access to such personal information;
  * The right to amend, delete, and/or restrict the processing of such personal information;
  * In some instances, the right to object to the processing of such personal information;
  * In some instances, the right to request that we export, in a structured, commonly used, machine readable, and interoperable format, and transmit to another controller, such personal information; and
  * The right to withdraw, at any time, any consent to the processing of such personal information.

To exercise these rights, please contact us at [dataprotectionofficer@kendrascott.com](mailto:dataprotectionofficer@kendrascott.com) and as a reminder, you may always log in and amend the information you provided to establish your account.

We may transfer your personal information to locations outside of the European Economic Area, including the United States. When we do, we use Standard Contractual Clauses, and some of our Service Providers may rely on Standard Contractual Clauses, Privacy Shield, or Binding Corporate Rules, to help ensure we and our Service Providers respect your privacy rights and protect the transfer your personal information to the United States, where it will be processed and stored. 

## How To Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described above, please contact us at [service@kendrascott.com.](mailto:service@kendrascott.com) You also have the right to submit feedback to the applicable supervisory authority in your jurisdiction of residence.

## Revisions To This Policy

We reserve the right to revise this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will post any changes on this website. You can tell if the Policy has changed by checking the “Last Revision” date that appears at the top of the Policy. If we change the Privacy Policy in a material way, we will provide appropriate notice to you.

* * *

[1] For purchases made by customers located outside of the U.S., Kendra Scott uses a third-party provider called Borderfree to service these purchases. An international customer may create an account with Borderfree and provide their payment information using their payment gateway. You can find Borderfree’s Privacy Policy here [](https://www.borderfree.com/privacy/en_us/#2.)https://www.borderfree.com/privacy/en_us/#2.
